(Penny:)What do you want me to tell you,
Sheldon?
l want you to tell me
that Howard is being mean to me for no reason.
(Penny:)Fine. Howard is being mean to you
for no reason.
l knew it.
- What's the matter?
- Every time I spend the night...
(Bernadette:)...your mom slaps me on the behind
and says, "Go get'em."
It's not her fauIt.
She's getting hormone-replacement therapy.
(Howard:)Makes her crazy horny.
(Howard:)Check this out. I got Sheldon
to wear the French maid's costume.
(Bernadette:)My God, that's terrible.
What?
Hey, I gave you first crack at it.
(Bernadette:)Why are you doing that?
You're being mean to him.
He's mean all the time.
(Howard:)You've heard him tease me
about not having a doctorate.
You don't wanna get teased about that,
get a doctorate.
l have one. They're great.